// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What Spider-Man Actor Has A Tattoo Of Their Spider-Emblem And Where Is It On Their Body?",
    answer: "Tom Holland, on the bottom of his foot",
    options: [
      "Andrew Garfield, on his buttocks",
      "Tobey Maguire, on his arm",
      "Tom Holland, on the bottom of his foot",
      "None, No Spider-Man actor has gotten a tattoo"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is Spider-Man’s 6th Sense Called?",
    answer: "Spidey-Sense",
    options: [
      "Spidey-Sense",
      "Arachnid Awareness",
      "Future Feeling",
      "Tingles"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which Of These is NOT a Spider-Man Villain?",
    answer: "Professor Pyg",
    options: [
      "Man-Wolf",
      "Professor Pyg",
      "The Spot",
      "Bigwheel"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What Year Was The First Spider-Man Comic Released?",
    answer: "1962",
    options: [
      "1972",
      "1981",
      "1962",
      "1959"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which Of These is NOT One Of Spider-Man’s Love Interests?",
    answer: "Selina Kyle",
    options: [
      "Selina Kyle",
      "Mary Jane Watson",
      "Felicia Hardy",
      "Betty Brant"
    ]
  },

     {
     numb: 6,
     question: "What Spider-Man Viillain Is In The Following Image?",
     answer: "Venom",
     options: [
       "Carnage",
       "Riot",
       "Venom",
       "Ant-Venom"
     ]
   },

   {
     numb: 7,
     question: "Which Version Of Spider-Man is This?",
     answer: "Superior Spider-Man",
     options: [
       "Ultimate Spider-Man",
       "Savage Spider-Man",
       "Superior Spider-Man",
       "Scarlet Spider"
     ]
   },

   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "Who Was The First Actor To Portray Spider-Man In Live Action?",
     answer: "Danny Seagren",
     options: [
       "Tobey Maguire",
       "Nicholas Hammond",
       "Danny Seagren",
       "Shinji Tōdō’s Takuya Yamashiro"
     ]
   },

   {
     numb: 9,
     question: "What Newspaper Does Spider-Man work for?",
     answer: "The Daily Bugle",
     options: [
       "The Daily Planet",
       "The Daily Bugle",
       "The Daily News",
       "The Daily Globe"
     ]
   },

   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Stan Lee Was The Creator Of Spider-Man, But Who Else Created The Main Art For Spider-Man?",
     answer: "Steve Ditko",
     options: [
       "Jared Lee",
       "Michael Janssen",
       "Steve Ditko",
       "Edward Halton"
     ]
   },
];